it's time to learn about animation or
是时候学习动漫或者
more specifically key frame animation
更具体地说 关键帧动画
because character animation with its
因为角色动画带有它的
Rigs and bones and things is its own
钻机、骨头和东西都是它自己的
entire separate Beast we're not going to
完全分开的野兽 我们不会
get into we're just going to do a very
上车吧 我们要做一个非常
simple camera move specifically we want
简单的相机移动特别是我们想要的
the camera to start above the donuts and
从甜甜圈上方开始的相机和
then fall down to reveal the final plate
然后倒下 露出最后一个盘子
uh at the end right it's an excuse to
呃 在最后的右边 这是一个借口
learn about key framing well the basics
了解如何构建好关键框架的基础知识
of Animation is really simple if you go
如果你去看动画片真的很简单
to the bottom of your screen if you're
到屏幕底部 如果您是
in layout
在布局中
uh layout at the layout layout at the
呃布局在布局布局在
top uh we can drag up on this divider
顶部 呃 我们可以拖到这个隔板上
here and you can see we've got a
在这里 您可以看到我们有一个
timeline which if I click and drag
时间线 如果我单击并拖动
across is currently doing nothing
Cross目前什么都不做
because there is no animation so if we
因为没有动画 所以如果我们
pull out right I'm just going to do a
向右开 我要做一次
really simple animation to show you you
非常简单的动画演示给你看
don't have to follow this because this
不必遵循这一点 因为这
is a different animation what we're
是一部不同于我们的动画
going to do it animation is really
去做它的动画真的是
simple you select the object that you
只需简单地选择您想要的对象
want to apply a key frame to and then
我要将关键帧应用于 然后
you hit I I for insert key frame frame
您按I I表示插入关键帧
and you get this like scary looking menu
你会看到这个看起来很可怕的菜单
apparently they're going to change this
显然他们要改变这一点
eventually but for now you would place a
最终 但现在您会将一个
key frame on what it is you're planning
关于你的计划的关键框架
to animate so in this case it's the
要设置动画 在本例中是
location right so I want to move the
位置正确 所以我想要移动
camera location then I change my frame
相机的位置 然后我改变我的画面
count to be the frame I want it to end
计数是我希望它结束的帧
at then I move the object how I want it
然后我以我想要的方式移动对象
to move right there and then I add
搬到那里 然后我加一句
another key frame I and then say
另一个关键帧 然后说
location and now as I play it back which
位置 现在当我回放它的时候
I can do by hitting space bar you can
我可以通过按空格键来做到这一点
see that the camera is moving haha look
看到摄像机在移动哈哈看
at us right a very simple camera move
在我们的右手边 一个非常简单的镜头移动
now I don't actually want that though so
不过 我其实并不想这样 所以
I'm going to delete those key frames um
我要删除那些关键帧 嗯
and what we want is we want what I
我们想要的是我们想要的东西
showed you at the start we want our
一开始就告诉你我们想要我们的
camera to start uh up here right rotated
摄像机从这里开始 呃 向右旋转
pointing down this way and then we want
指向这个方向 然后我们想要
it to move in an arc uh in this
它在这个里面呢是做弧形运动的
direction terrible Arrow um pointed this
方向可怕的箭头 嗯 指向这个
way right now you could do this you
现在你可以做到这一点
could move the camera up there you could
可以把摄像机移到上面 你可以
then rotate it to point it down and then
然后旋转它将其指向下方 然后
do a key frame for the location rotation
为位置旋转做一个关键帧
and then do another one over here but it
然后在这里再做一个 但它
would be very difficult to control that
是很难控制的
movement and really this is a rather
运动 这真的是一个相当大的
simple movement if we have a pivot
如果我们有一个枢轴 就可以简单地移动
object if we have something here and
如果我们这里有什么东西 我反对
then we parent that camera to that
然后我们将摄像机设置为该对象的子对象
object and then we just rotate that
对象 然后我们只需旋转它
object it's a lot easier so what we need
反对 这要容易得多 所以我们需要的是
to add is uh first of all I want to
要补充的是 嗯 首先我想
think what do I want to be the center of
想一想我想成为什么的中心
it what do I want to be where do I want
我想要什么？我想去哪里？
that pivot object so I think you know
那个枢轴对象 所以我想你知道
somewhere roughly in the middle of these
大概在这些中间的某个地方
Donuts so right here I'm going to hold
甜甜圈所以就在这里我要拿着
down shift and then right click and
按Shift键 然后单击鼠标右键并
that's going to put my 3D cursor um
这将把我的3D光标嗯
right where I've put it and now to add
就在我放它的地方 现在要添加
an object shift a and I'm looking for
一个物体移动了a 我正在寻找
empty so an empty I mean if you're
空虚所以空虚我是说如果你
familiar with other creative tools you
熟悉其他创意工具
probably already know but it's just
可能已经知道了 但只是
something it's uh similar to a null
一些东西 呃 类似于零
object in After Effects Etc it's just
后效中的物体等等 它只是
something that's going to be in the 3D
一些将会出现在3D中的东西
view Port that won't be rendered okay a
不会正常渲染的视窗a
number of options here it doesn't matter
选择的数量在这里并不重要
which one you choose you can go plain
你选择哪一个你可以选择平淡无奇
axes uh and then if you went to the
斧头 嗯 然后如果你去了
options here the data you could change
此处的选项您可以更改的数据
the display here to what we saw um
这里的展示就是我们所看到的
before but this is just like a different
但这就像是一种不同的
display um object right depending on
根据以下内容显示um对象右侧
what you're looking for I think the
你要找的东西我认为
sphere is actually the most useful it's
球体实际上是最有用的它是
way too big currently so I'm going to
现在太大了 所以我要
change the size to be something about
把大小改成大概
that and there we go okay so now what we
好了 现在我们要做的就是
need to do is we want to parent our
需要做的是我们想要为我们的
camera to this new empty object so
相机对准这个新的空物体 所以
select the camera first then shift
先选择相机 然后按Shift键
select that new empty that we've just
选择我们刚刚创建的新空格
created and then I'm going to hit contrl
创建 然后我要按下Ctrl
p and then set parent object keep
P 然后设置父对象KEEP
transform just like what we did um with
就像我们所做的那样进行改造
the icing and the donut so now you
糖衣和甜甜圈所以现在你
should see if you select that empty and
应该会看到您是否选择了该空的
as I rotate it around the camera will
当我绕着摄像机旋转它的时候
rotate with it and if you look through
用它旋转 如果你透过它看
the camera with numpad zero and then
数字键盘为零的相机 然后
just double tap r you can see that I can
只需双击R 你就会看到我可以
track ball rotate around it um and you
轨迹球绕着它旋转 嗯 然后你
can see this is like way more flexible
可以看到这就像是更灵活的方式
for what we want we want the camera to
为了我们想要的 我们想让摄像机
be focused on one point and then we just
只专注于一点 然后我们就
want to move the camera around that
想要在那里移动摄像机吗？
point um and you can do some really nice
嗯 你可以做一些非常好的事情
fast camera moves here if you wanted to
如果你想的话快速摄像机就会移动到这里
do something snazzy in our case we're
在我们的情况下做一些时髦的事情 我们
going to do a nice simple slow movement
我要做一个很好的简单的慢动作
so first of all this angle this look
所以首先这个角度 这个眼神
that we've got right here is where we
我们现在所拥有的就是我们
want the final reveal to be so this is
想要最后的揭晓是这样的
where I want the end point the End Key
我想要结束点的位置结束键
frame of my animation to be so you can
我的动画的框架 这样你就可以
make your animation as long as you want
想做多久就做多久的动画
I think about 160 frames is about right
我认为160张左右的照片是对的
for this sort of uh the the the speed of
对于这种 呃 速度
this animation so on frame 160 there you
在第160帧的动画中 您可以
can see it's also mentioned there I'm
看得出来 上面也提到了我
going to with my empty selected not my
用我的空选择而不是我的
camera I'm going to hit I and then not
我要按下I 然后就不拍了
select location like I did before but
像我以前一样选择位置 但是
rotation because we're going to be just
轮换 因为我们将只是
rotating that Pivot Point not changing
旋转该轴心点不变
its um its position so rotation then I'm
它 它的位置 所以旋转 然后我
going to go to the first frame which I
我要转到第一帧 我
could do by clicking and dragging or
可以通过单击并拖动或
shift left Arrow will jump you to the
Shift向左箭头键将跳转到
first uh frame or you can click these
首先 呃 框 或者你可以点击这些
little um I don't know you call that
小 嗯 我不知道你这么叫
button jump to end point um you can do
按钮跳转到终点嗯你可以这样做
that as well and now that I'm here I'm
也是如此 现在我在这里 我在
going to rotate this along not the Tilt
要沿着这个方向旋转 而不是倾斜
axis which it is by default but the x
轴 默认情况下为该轴 但x
axis aha right so now you can see we're
轴心啊哈所以现在你可以看到我们
doing that exact move we want and in the
做我们想做的那一步 在
top left hand corner you can see the
您可以在左上角看到
exact number of degrees um and I'm going
准确的度数 嗯 我要去
to go with exactly minus 90 so if you
正好是零下90度 所以如果你
hold down control you can see it's
按住Ctrl 你可以看到它是
snapping to uh minus 90 and then I'm
猛冲到呃零下90度 然后我
going to click okay now before I change
在我更改之前 现在要点击OK
my my frame if I was to change the frame
如果我换了画框 我的画框
um you can see it's just snapped me back
嗯 你可以看到 它刚刚把我拉回来了
to where I were so always remember you
去我一直记得你的地方
have to create a key frame if you've
必须创建一个关键帧 如果您有
changed its movement without saving it
在没有保存的情况下更改了它的移动
or without putting in a new key frame so
或者不放入新的关键帧
back up to here minus 90 and I'm going
回到这里-90 我就走了
to hit I and then say rotation okay and
击打我 然后说旋转好的
now we should see if we hit space bar to
现在我们应该看看是否按空格键
play a very very simple
玩一个非常非常简单的
animation okay now we can tweak this
动画好的 现在我们可以调整这个了
though we can improve this because you
虽然我们可以改进这一点 因为你
can see that for one it's a little
可以看出 对于一个人来说 这是一个有点
awkward that the camera starts in a
令人尴尬的是 摄像机是从一个
completely stationary stop position then
然后完全静止的停止位置
it ramps up and then it slows down
它加速 然后又减慢
towards the end it's a little bit of a
接近尾声时 这有点像是
weird camera move what I want instead is
奇怪的相机移动 我想要的是
I want it to start I already want it to
我想要它开始我已经想要它了
be moving right like almost like it's
向右移动 就像它几乎
from another shot that's kind of faded
从另一张褪色的照片中
into this one I want it to start moving
我想让它开始移动
and then to much more slowly fade it out
然后慢慢地把它淡出
than it is currently CU you can see it
比当前的CU更高 你可以看到它
just kind of like drops down here and
就像在这里掉落 然后
then the camera just stops and it's a
然后摄像机就停了下来 这是一个
little too sudden and while you could
有点太突然了 虽然你可以
change the key frames here like you can
尽可能地更改此处的关键帧
do some very simple uh handle type
做一些非常简单的呃手柄类型
changes this view this layout view is
更改此视图此布局视图为
not the best place to do this so instead
不是做这件事的最好地方
if you go to the animation tab at the
如果转到动画选项卡 请访问
top there you can see it's again it's
在上面你可以看到它又是它是
rearranged all your screens um this over
重新排列了你们所有的屏幕 嗯 这个
here is just another 3D view over here
这只是另一张3D图
is the camera uh the camera view but at
相机 呃 是相机视角 但在
the bottom here you can see we've
在这里的底部你可以看到我们已经
changed from the timeline which is what
改变了时间线 这就是
we had before and it's changed to a dope
我们以前有过 但现在变成了毒品
sheet so a dope sheet is just going to
所以一张毒品单就是为了
show you more information
向您显示更多信息
um about the key frames so for example
嗯 关于关键帧 例如
you can see that the X rotation has a
您可以看到 X轴旋转有一个
DOT over here and a DOT over here but
这里是点 这里是点 但是
the Y and the Zed um has a different
Y和ZED UM有不同的
look it's got a continuous line across
看 它有一条连续的横跨
it and that's to show you that this
这和那是为了向你们展示这一点
actually hasn't changed that the Y and
实际上并没有改变Y和
the Zed has no information that's uh
ZED没有任何信息 呃
changed from the start to the end so we
从头到尾都变了 所以我们
don't actually need these key frames so
并不需要这些关键帧 所以
I only need the X rotation so I'm going
我只需要X轮换 所以我要去
to select the Y and the Zed and I'm just
选择Y和ZED 我只是
going to delete them just by hitting the
要删除它们 只需点击
delete key so we've now just got one
删除密钥 这样我们现在只有一个密钥
channel that the animation is happening
动画正在发生的频道
on right but we can't really change it
是正确的 但我们不能真正改变它
we can't make it so this starts faster
我们赶不上了 所以开始得更快
and then this slows down from this view
然后 从这个角度看 这个速度变慢了
instead we need to change to a different
相反 我们需要改变为一个不同的
view so in the top leftand Corner click
查看左上角 然后单击
this and we're going to change the
这就是我们要改变
window type to be graph editor okay so
窗口类型要成为图形编辑器 好的 所以
the graph editor looks like this I'm
图形编辑器看起来像这样：我是
going to use middle Mouse to uh pan
要用鼠标中键来呃平移
around here and you can see we've now
在这附近 你可以看到我们现在
got a line right with some handles on it
有一条线 上面有几个把手
which is a lot easier to understand but
这很容易理解 但是
it's hard to get it all in the view so
很难把它全部呈现在视野中 所以
you could hit the home key and that will
你可以按下Home键 它就会
automatically reorient everything um to
自动将所有对象um重新定向到
position it in the view or if you hold
将其放置在视图中 或者如果您按住
down control and middle Mouse button
向下控制和鼠标中键
this enables you to just moving around
这使您能够只需移动
just dragging around control middle
只是在控件中间拖动
Mouse button will change the uh the axis
鼠标按键会改变这个轴
Zoom as well as the Y right up and down
向上和向下缩放以及Y键
like that um which is just a really
就像那个 嗯 就是一个真正的
handy way to quickly Orient yourself
快速定位自己的便捷方法
around so control middle Mouse to change
左右键控制 鼠标中键改变
this and then you can uh middle Mouse to
这个 然后你可以用鼠标中键
pan to a different area Okay so again
平移到不同的区域好的 再来一次
making sure I'm looking at the X
确保我看到的是X
rotation there right and if we look you
在那里旋转 如果我们看着你
should see the problem that we have
应该看到我们所面临的问题
right we have the start of the animation
好的 我们开始播放动画了
it's a very slow curve that's going up
这是一条非常缓慢的上升曲线
it picks up speed in the middle uh and
它在中间加速 呃 然后
then it ends here and the end is a
然后它在这里结束 结束是一个
little abrupt considering uh the amount
考虑到 呃 金额 有点突然
of movement that it has so really we
它的运动 所以我们真的
want um this line instead to look a
我想让这条线看起来像是
little bit closer to this line right or
离这条线近一点 对不对？
even I mean that was kind of a bad line
即使我是说那是一句很糟糕的台词
pull it rather like that okay that's the
就像这样拉好了 这就是
kind of look that we want so with our
我们想要的那种外观所以我们的
starting key frame here I'm going to use
开始关键帧在这里 我将使用
the same hotkey that you use everywhere
您在任何地方使用的相同热键
uh and that's R um to just get that
呃 这就是Rum拿到的
angle to look a lot closer to what I
角度看起来更接近我的
want don't go too far up if you go like
如果你像这样 不要走得太高
vertical you'll see that the start is
垂直的 你会看到起点是
like so abrupt it's almost like it's
就像是如此突然 几乎就像
like skipping down or something so I
就像跳下去之类的 所以我
don't want it to be that far I'm going
我不想走那么远 我要去
to rotate a little bit out like that so
像这样向外旋转一点 这样
there's a little bit of a harsh movement
有一点刺耳的动作
but not too harsh if you know what I
但不会太苛刻 如果你知道我
mean there we go something like that and
意思是我们在那里做一些类似的事情
then for this end bit you can see it
那么你可以看到这个结尾的部分
ends rather suddenly maybe you disagree
结束得很突然 也许你不同意
but I found when I looked at the
但我发现当我看着
animation it was rather sudden so this
这是相当突然的 所以这
final end point here I'm going to scale
最后的终点在这里 我要扩展
It Out by hitting s so again same
就这样又打了S一顿就了结了
hotkeys work all across blender which is
热键在搅拌机中都可以使用 这是
very nice awesome so now if I play it
非常好 太棒了 现在如果我演奏它
back you should see it moves rather fast
在后面 你应该看到它移动得相当快
at the beginning and then slowly tapers
在开始时 然后慢慢地逐渐减少
out out towards the end to a nice soft
在接近尾声的时候出来了一个漂亮的柔软的
Landing which is really cool and that's
着陆 这真的很酷 这是
pretty well yeah that's a pretty good
很好 是的 这是一个很好的
animation now we could stop here but the
动画现在我们可以止步于此 但是
other thing we could do to get a little
我们可以做的另一件事
bit more Motion in it is we could have
更多的动感是我们可以有
the camera start closer to the donuts
摄像机从靠近甜甜圈的地方开始
and then pull out as it goes further
然后随着它的进一步发展而退出
away I hate that this keeps uh
离开 我讨厌这让呃
interrupting I'm going to hide that okay
打断一下 我要把它藏起来 好吗
there we go select my Pivot there we go
我们来选择我的枢轴我们来吧
so uh essentially we could have it so
所以 呃 基本上我们可以这样做
that it starts like the camera starts
它开始的时候就像摄像机启动一样
right about here and then it pulls out
就在这里 然后它就出来了
and then as it pulls out it goes a
然后 当它拉出时 它会发出一个
little bit further away and like ends
距离更远一点 就像是尽头
back here so have a think about how you
回到这里 想一想你是如何
would do that how would you have the
会这么做的话你怎么会有
camera start closer to the pivot point
相机开始距离轴心点更近
right now you might think well okay we
现在你可能会觉得很好 好吧 我们
could animate the camera pulling in
可以将相机拉入的动画设置为
closer but that would be overly
更近了 但那太过分了
complicated we can just use the same
复杂的是 我们可以使用相同的
pivot point but we can scale it because
轴心点 但我们可以扩展它 因为
you can see if I hit s look at that the
你看 如果我打了S 看那个
camera goes closer and if I pull it out
摄像机走近一些 如果我把它拿出来
you can see the camera moves f further
你可以看到相机在进一步移动
away so what I want to do is I want to
所以我想做的是我想
go to the uh the final Endo here the
去 呃 最后的Endo在这里
frame 160 which by the way you can jump
第160帧 顺便说一下 你可以跳
to an existing key frame just by using
添加到现有关键帧 只需使用
the up and down arrows so if I go up you
向上和向下的箭头 所以如果我上了你
can see it's uh that key frame or down
可以看到它是呃关键帧还是向下
it uh takes me to the front so I want to
它呃把我带到了前面 所以我想
go here and I want to create uh a key
去这里 我想创建一个 呃 钥匙
frame just for the scale information so
仅用于比例尺信息 因此
here cuz this is the end view that I
因为这是我看到的最后一幅图
want so I'm going to hit I and then say
所以我要打我然后说
not rotation but scale so now I'm going
不是旋转 而是比例 所以我现在要去
to go to the front of the animation and
转到动画的最前面 然后
I'm going to scale it in to get a nice
我要把它放大 得到一个很好的
closeup of the donuts right there and
甜甜圈的特写就在那里
then I'm going to add another key frame
然后我要添加另一个关键帧
I and then scale so you should now see
我 然后扩展 所以你现在应该看到
in your graph editor that's what it's
在您的图形编辑器中 这就是它
called um you should see your rotation
我叫 嗯 你应该看看你的轮换
information and then your scale
信息 然后是你的秤
information now you'll know that the
信息现在你就会知道
scale is like like where is the scale
规模就像规模在哪里
information it's here but it's so small
信息它就在这里 但它太小了
like the amount of uh variant here it's
就像这里的呃变种的量一样
so small that it it's just not readable
太小了 根本读不懂
and the reason for that is that it's
这么做的原因是
trying to combine two different data
尝试合并两个不同的数据
types into one view right because
正确地输入到一个视图中 因为
rotation is happening on a you can see
旋转发生在你可以看到的
here it's a oh I just wrote over the top
这是一个哦 我刚刚在上面写的
of it it's 0 degre and then down here
它是0度 然后往下走
you've got minus 90 so this is a minus
你得到了负90分 所以这是负分
90 right but then up here we've got
90对 但在这上面我们有
scale that's happening between a zero
发生在零之间的比例
range and a one range which is right
范围和一个正确的范围
next to it okay so one you could just
在它旁边 好的 这样你就可以
hide your rotation or you can click on
隐藏您的旋转 或者您可以点击
normalize and normalize will uh put
正常化和正常化将呃放在
everything between a zero to one range
从0到1范围内的所有东西
but just know that when you're in this
但要知道 当你身处其中时
range if you try to move a key frame to
如果您尝试将关键帧移动到
be a different value like you took your
成为一种不同的价值 就像你拿了你的
scale and then you moved it down when
缩放 然后当您向下移动它时
you confirm it it'll snap back to where
你确认一下 它就会回到原来的位置
it was and that's because with normalize
是的 那是因为有了Normize
on it'll always put everything between 0
它总是会把所有的东西都放在0
to 1 so don't do it if you're planning
比1 所以如果你计划的话就不要做了
to change a value of something normalize
改变某物的正常值
um but other otherwise it's uh it's okay
嗯 但其他方面呢 呃 没关系
to use for changing the handles like in
用于更改手柄 如中
this case but I'm going to hide my
但我要把我的
rotation anyway cuz it's just going to
不管怎么说 旋转是因为它只会
get in the way um and instead you can
挡道 嗯 相反 你可以
see that x y and Zed all have
看看x y和zed都有
information in them because of course
当然是因为它们里面的信息
we're not scaling it on any particular
我们不会在任何特定情况下对其进行衡量
axis it's across all three axes at once
轴它同时横跨所有三个轴
because it's like a yeah it's the
因为这就像是 是的 这是
uniform value of
的一致值
scale so um again I could do the same
规模 所以我也可以做同样的事情
thing here I could rotate this I don't
这里的东西我可以旋转这个我不
want there to be too much of a
希望有太多的
difference like it's actually pretty
不同之处在于它实际上很漂亮
good by default like the scale isn't as
默认情况下是好的 因为比例不是
noticeable that it slowly ramps up um
值得注意的是 它慢慢地上升 嗯
and it's good to have like a kind of a
这很好 就像一种
softer movement as it pulls away but I
当它离开时 它会轻轻地移动 但我
do want to change it a little bit I'm
我真的想改一下吗？我
going to select these final end points
我要选择这些最终终点
I'll scale that out a little bit as well
我也会稍微扩展一下
just so it's a little softer as it
只是为了让它更柔和一点
scales
鳞片
out and that is pretty good
出局 这是相当好的
folks now you'll note as I play through
伙计们 你们现在会注意到我演奏的过程
this that in the top leftand corner of
这是在左上角的那个
the screen you've got FPS which stands
屏幕上显示的是FPS
for frames per second if you play video
播放视频时的每秒帧数
games you're already well familiar with
你已经很熟悉的游戏
that term uh and you can see as we play
这个术语 呃 你可以在我们演奏的时候看到
through it it can't really make up its
通过它 它不能真正弥补它的
mind it's like 24 no 25 26 24 it's I
注意 就像是24不25 26 24是我
think it's just a readout glitch in in
我认为这只是一个读数故障
blunder it's actually a constant 24
大错特错 实际上是一个常量24
frames per second by default but for
默认情况下为每秒帧数 但对于
whatever reason it's kind of like
不管是什么原因 这就像是
fluctuating between them anyway point is
不管怎样 在他们之间波动的重点是
is you can change that amount by going
你可以通过以下方式改变这个数字
to your output settings over here and
添加到您的输出设置中 然后
then underneath format you've got frame
然后在Format下面是Frame
rate now for whatever reason blunder
不管是什么原因造成的失误 现在收视率
chose 24 frames per second which is
选择了每秒24帧 即
really only used for feature film
真的只用在故事片上
everyone else for like TV or YouTube
其他人都喜欢看电视或YouTube
it's 30 frames per second you can also
每秒30帧 你还可以
uh go 60 frames per second if you wanted
呃 如果你想的话可以达到每秒60帧
to really pay for longer render times
要真正为更长的渲染时间买单
because it means things uh have to be
因为这意味着事情 呃 必须是
you have to render like twice as many
您必须渲染两倍的数量
frames but it means things are buttery
但这意味着一切都是黄油的
smooth you won't actually see it right
平滑 你不会真的看到它
now because I'm recording this tutorial
现在 因为我正在录制这篇教程
at 30 frames per second anyways really
以每秒30帧的速度真的
the the options that most people choose
大多数人选择的选项
are 24 for Cinema and feature films 30
电影院24部 故事片30部
if you're a normal person and you're
如果你是一个普通人 你是
making things for internet or YouTube or
为互联网或YouTube或
anything and then 60 if it's for like 3D
任何东西 然后60 如果是3D的话
content or something that has to be
内容或一些必须是
really really smooth anyways we're going
真的很顺利无论如何我们要去
to set it to 30 cuz that is the more
将其设置为30立方英尺 这是更多
standard frame rate for uh for most
大多数情况下的标准帧速率
things I know people like to argue but
我知道人们喜欢争论的事情 但是
yes 30 is in my opinion a much more
是的 30岁在我看来要多得多
reasonable uh frame rate for most things
大多数东西的合理的 呃 帧速率
and the final thing you'll note um as we
最后你们要注意的是 当我们
play through this is that it gets to
这件事的关键是它会变成
frame 160 and then it just kind of
第160帧 然后它就像是
pauses for a bit until it gets to frame
暂停一段时间 直到它到达帧
250 and then it Loops back and that is
然后它循环回来 那就是
because uh the end frame is set to 250
因为呃结束帧设置为250
so if we set this to 160 instead which
因此 如果我们将其设置为160
is what our animation ends at you can
是我们的动画结束时你可以看到的
see it will now play through and it'll
看 它现在将播放完 它将
get to the end and then it will loop
走到尽头 它就会循环
back to the start and also if you want
回到起点 如果你想
to like reset this this uh this view in
就像重置这个 这个 这个视图
your timeline you can hit the home key
你的时间线你可以按下Home键
and that'll like expand it out a little
这就像是把它扩大了一点
bit um and there you go so that is
嗯 然后你就可以了 就这样
basically our final animation you can
基本上我们的最终动画你可以
tweak it you can make it look a little
调整一下 你可以让它看起来有点
bit more polished than what I have here
比我这里的更精致一点
cuz when I'm recording a tutorial I can
因为当我录制教程时 我可以
only do so much before people get bored
只有在人们感到厌烦之前才能做这么多
um but that's that's pretty good it's
嗯 但那很好 很好
not bad so we are nearing the end go
不错 所以我们已经接近尾声了
ahead click here to join me in what
点击这里加入我的行列
might be the final part uh we're going
可能是最后一部分呃我们要去
to do rendering and forming that uh that
进行渲染和形成那个呃那个
final animation so click there and I
最后的动画 点击那里 我
will see you there
我会在那里见到你